What?
Lord Severin?
What’s wrong, Lord Campbell?
Do you know him?
Of course I know him.
I became Lord of the
Wastelands
because Lord Severin guided me.
What?!
Lord Campbell,
are you saying he helped
you become Lord of
the Wastelands?
I must have misheard.
I rule the
entire Wastelands.
I would
never joke about something like this.
But he was disowned by House Carter
and became a worthless miner.
How could he possibly help you?
Lady Livia, you are wrong.
Lord Severin is a
man of heaven-defying power.
I don’t know his
true identity, but years ago,
with just two sentences,
he pulled my family
back from the brink of
destruction and made me
Lord of the entire Wastelands.
Lord Severin is a
true god of Golantis.
So when you helped
my family…
it was on his orders?
Yes.
Not only that.
Every time you faced a
crisis these past
three years and survived,
it was because Lord Severin
secretly ordered help for you.
This can't be.
This is impossible.